What kind of sparks can Seedance2.0 and Lobster create together?
The first use case that comes to my mind
that is, integrating Seedance2.0 within Lobster to generate e-commerce videos
and then upload the product video along with the product description
automatically input into the e-commerce system
achieve a one-stop service
So can this feature be achieved?
The answer is yes
Now, let's proceed to implement the most crucial step first
First, integrate Seedance2.0 into Lobster to generate e-commerce videos
Alright, let's take a look at the results first.
Then I'll explain to you how it's actually implemented.
So I have already integrated Seedance2.0 into Lobster.
Not only can I generate videos
and also able to use the latest image generation 5.0 from a certain platform
unlimited free image generation
This is all possible
Well, our focus is not on image generation.
Let's take a look at how to use Lobster to connect with our Seedance2.0
generate e-commerce images
Okay, now then, let's open our Lobster tool
on my desktop
You can see there is a photo of a teapot.
Next, I'll have Lobster fetch this image from the desktop
and then generate the corresponding e-commerce image
Okay, now let's open Lobster
give it a description
Use the teapot image on my computer desktop
call the latest video generation skill
Generate a 5-second product introduction video for the disinfectant
Of course, right now for the sake of speed
I have it generate a 5-second one
It can generate up to 15 seconds at most.
So this duration can be customized according to our needs.
Alright, then next, after we finish entering the content
we just need to click send
But here, this is a product introduction video, right?
Ah, change it to video, okay
Then click send
At this point, our large model
starts to invoke Mumeng's Seedance2.0
started generating the video
Let's wait a moment to see the results.
Alright, after a while,
The video is finally generated.
So how about the quality of the generated content?
Next, let's open the directory
Let's take a look at the final rendered video.
Alright, so you can see the images in the video
It's my picture
This remains unchanged.
Then click to view, savoring time that begins with a cup of clear tea is quite nice.
Five seconds, of course we can also make it longer
up to 15 seconds
Here I have set it to five seconds.
So here we are
we have achieved the functionality of automatically generating videos using Lobster
Then, we can use it as a node later on
then we don't need to connect it to other automated processes
for example, to publish this video
automatically publish to e-commerce platforms, etc.
all of this can be done
Well, here comes the question
How is this technology implemented?
Next, let's take a look at the specific technical implementation together.
So how is it implemented?
Let me briefly explain to everyone.
Let's start with the flowchart.
For example, my Lobster tool first simulates a user
This user is actually me, simulating a user
First, obtain the user's identity information
After that, once the identity information is obtained,
then go to the video generation website
simulate user requests to generate videos
Then after generating this video
then download it to my local device
This is the entire execution process.
However, during this execution process,
OK, it involves a relay service.
This relay service
a website will be deployed locally
Then this website initiates a simulated request
and finally
forward this request to the video generation website
This is how it's implemented
So locally, there will be a relay service
So this relay service
where it is, let me show you
this API
It is a relay service
Then, with this relay service in place
OK Me lobster is configured with skills
it can be invoked
Alright, this is the specific implementation flowchart.
Now that we have this flowchart
So what exactly is the technical implementation?
Let me explain to you
First of all, OK, there are two steps
First, use the Docker method
the relay service
which is this service
then deploy it locally
Using this command, you can directly execute the deployment command.
After the deployment command is completed
Access this URL
If such a message appears
It's not a 404.
then it means your service has successfully started
After the service is successfully started,
Next, go to the repository to download his skills
Save these skills to your Lobster skills directory
That's it.
After saving it,
DIK instruct your Lobster to learn the skills inside
and locate your Extreme Dream session ID
then set it to your Lobster
After setting it up, OK
you can just send commands like I do
generate images for free
or use credits to generate videos, alright
This is the entire technical implementation.
Well, some people might be concerned at this point
Then Brother Lei, if I use Lobster to do it this way
Does it consume a lot of tokens?
The answer is yes.
Lobster sends the current context as tokens to the large model each time.
So this entire execution process may consume a significant amount of tokens.
So is there any way
allow me to use tokens at a low cost
Hey, I actually found a package here
For just 7 yuan, you can get 29 million credits
The ratio of credits to tokens is
almost at a ratio of 3:1 or 4:1
That means the TOKEN you can consume
input TOKEN and output TOKEN
7 yuan can purchase approximately 10 million TOKENs
It's a fantastic deal!
The current lowest price in the domestic market
3 yuan for 1 million TOKENs
then 10 million tokens would cost you 30 yuan
However, this one only costs seven yuan.
If the seven yuan package is not enough for you
There is also a 50-yuan package available here
7 million credits per day
And this is not important
This is not the most important thing
The most important thing is OK, as you can see
Inside, I can use Company A's 4.5 model
Brothers, the 4.5 model!
and the 5.2 model from Company O
models, all of these are available
Monthly subscription provides ample quantity
So what else is there to say
Brothers, take action now
I'm Brother Li
share a valuable tip every day